export const hipHopQuestions = [
  {
    question: "This Hip-Hop Legend, produced Soul4Real's Candy Rain",
    answers: {
      choices: ["Heavy D", "Slick Rick", "Rakim", "Spoonie G"],
      correct: "Heavy D",
    },
  },
  {
    question: "Who is regarded as the Godfather of Hip-Hop?",
    answers: {
      choices: [
        "DJ Mustard",
        "DJ Kool Herc",
        "DJ AM",
        "DJ Jazzy Jeff & The Fresh Prince",
      ],
      correct: "DJ Kool Herc",
    },
  },
  {
    question: "Name one of the five elements of Hip-Hop?",
    answers: {
      choices: ["Twerking", "MC Battling", "Graffiti Art", "Dancing"],
      correct: "Graffiti Art",
    },
  },
  {
    question: "Alongside DJ Run and DMC who else is a member of Run DMC?",
    answers: {
      choices: ["Biz Markie", "Jam Master Jay", "Akon", "DMX"],
      correct: "Jam Master Jay",
    },
  },
  {
    question:
      "The album, Flesh of My Flesh, Blood of My Blood , was released by which hip hop group or artist?",
    answers: {
      choices: ["DMX", "Master P", "Kanye West", "Jay-Z"],
      correct: "DMX",
    },
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the first Billionaire in Hip-Hop?",
    answers: {
      choices: ["Kanye West", "Michael B. Jordan", "Rihanna", "Jay-Z"],
      correct: "Jay-Z",
    },
  },
  {
    question: "Brad Terrence Jordan is better known as what?",
    answers: {
      choices: ["Trick Daddy", "DMC", "Scarface", "Wiz Khalifa"],
      correct: "Scarface",
    },
  },
  {
    question:
      "How many Diamond records (10x's Platinum) are in Eminem's Catalogue?",
    answers: {
      choices: ["6", "3", "2", "5"],
      correct: "2",
    },
  },
  {
    question: "Which Notorious B.I.G album was released during his lifetime?",
    answers: {
      choices: ["No Way Out", "Born Again", "Life After Death", "Ready to Die"],
      correct: "Ready to Die",
    },
  },
  {
    question: "Pras is a member of which NJ-based band, formed in 1994?",
    answers: {
      choices: [
        "The Porgies",
        "All Dash Digital",
        "The Fugees",
        "Naughty-by-Nature",
      ],
      correct: "The Fugees",
    },
  },
  {
    question:
      "In what year was The Parental Advisory label introduced by the Recording Industry Association of America?",
    answers: {
      choices: ["1986", "1978", "1985", "1989"],
      correct: "1985",
    },
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the time between the mid-1980s and mid-1990s known as regarding Hip-Hop?",
    answers: {
      choices: [
        "The Rebirth",
        "The Prime Years",
        "The Sample Years",
        "The Golden Age",
      ],
      correct: "The Golden Age",
    },
  },
  {
    question: "What subgenre started the blend of Hip-Hop and R&B?",
    answers: {
      choices: ["Boom Bap", "Trap & B", "New Jack Swing", "Chipmunk Sampling"],
      correct: "New Jack Swing",
    },
  },
  {
    question:
      "This female singer is regarded as the Queen of Hip-Hop Soul. Who is she?",
    answers: {
      choices: ["Aaliyah", "Mariah Carey", "Mary J. Blige", "Ashanti"],
      correct: "Mary J. Blige",
    },
  },
  {
    question: "This female is regarded as the Queen of Rap. Who is she?",
    answers: {
      choices: ["Lil' Kim", "Cardi B", "NIcki Minaj", "Queen Latifah "],
      correct: "NIcki Minaj",
    },
  },
  {
    question: "What was the name of The Game's debut album in 2005?",
    answers: {
      choices: ["The Game", "The Truth", "The Show", "The Documentary"],
      correct: "The Documentary",
    },
  },
  {
    question: "Which hip hop star was the voice of Reptar on Rugrats?",
    answers: {
      choices: ["Busta Rhymes", "Q-Tip", "Biz Markie", "Doug E. Fresh"],
      correct: "Busta Rhymes",
    },
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of these albums from Nas has no tracks produced by DJ Premier?",
    answers: {
      choices: ["It Was Written", "Stillmatic", "God's Son", "Nastradamus"],
      correct: "God's Son",
    },
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which producer graduated from Harvard before their music career took off?",
    answers: {
      choices: ["Diddy", "Ryan Leslie", "Swizz Beatz", "Steven Jordan"],
      correct: "Ryan Leslie",
    },
  },
  {
    question: "John Jackson is better known to his fans as?",
    answers: {
      choices: ["RIck Ross", "Fabaolous", "Pusha T", "Lil' Yatchy"],
      correct: "Fabaolous",
    },
  },
];
